[{"id":1,"question":"Why is AWS more economical than traditional data centers for applications with varying compute workloads?","choiceA":"f Amazon EC2 costs are billed on a monthly basis","choiceB":"f Users retain full administrative access to their Amazon EC2 instances.","choiceC":"Amazon EC2 instances can be launched on demand when needed","choiceD":"f Users can permanently run enough instances to handle peak workloads.","id_correct":1},{"id":2,"question":"Which AWS service would simplify the migration of a database to AWS?","choiceA":"f AWS Storage Gateway","choiceB":"AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)","choiceC":"f Amazon EC2","choiceD":"f Amazon AppStream 2.0","id_correct":2},{"id":3,"question":"Which AWS offering enables users to find, buy, and immediately start using software solutions in their AWS environment?","choiceA":"f AWS Config","choiceB":"f AWS OpsWorks","choiceC":"f AWS SDK","choiceD":"AWS Marketplace","id_correct":3},{"id":4,"question":"Which AWS networking service enables a company to create a virtual network within AWS?","choiceA":"f AWS Config","choiceB":"f Amazon Route 53","choiceC":"f AWS Direct Connect","choiceD":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)","id_correct":4},{"id":5,"question":"Which of the following is an AWS responsibility under the AWS shared responsibility model?","choiceA":"f Configuring third-party applications","choiceB":"Maintaining physical hardware","choiceC":"f Securing application access and data","choiceD":"f Managing guest operating systems","id_correct":5},{"id":6,"question":"Which component of the AWS global infrastructure does Amazon CloudFront use to ensure low-latency delivery?","choiceA":"f AWS Regions","choiceB":"Edge locations","choiceC":"f Availability Zones","choiceD":"f Virtual Private Cloud (VPC)","id_correct":6},{"id":7,"question":"How would a system administrator add an additional layer of login security to a user's AWS Management Console?","choiceA":"f Use Amazon Cloud Directory","choiceB":"f Audit AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) roles","choiceC":"Enable multi-factor authentication","choiceD":"f Enable AWS CloudTrail","id_correct":7},{"id":8,"question":"Which service can identify the user that made the API call when an Amazon EC2 instance is terminated?","choiceA":"f AWS Trusted Advisor","choiceB":"AWS CloudTrail","choiceC":"f AWS X-Ray","choiceD":"f AWS Identity and Access Management (AWS IAM)","id_correct":8},{"id":9,"question":"Which service would be used to send alerts based on Amazon CloudWatch alarms?","choiceA":"Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)","choiceB":"f AWS CloudTrail","choiceC":"f AWS Trusted Advisor","choiceD":"f Amazon Route 53","id_correct":9},{"id":10,"question":"Where can a user find information about prohibited actions on the AWS infrastructure?","choiceA":"f AWS Trusted Advisor","choiceB":"f AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)","choiceC":"f AWS Billing Console","choiceD":"AWS Acceptable Use Policy","id_correct":10}]